���// JavaScript Document // Updated 03-19-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 03-30-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 03-31-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 04-09-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 04-14-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-01-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-08-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-21-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-26-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-27-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-28-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-29-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-04-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-05-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-08-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-09-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-10-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-11-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-17-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 07-01-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 07-24-2015 | Tammy Ritterskamp - TR108R // // Updated 07-27-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 07-29-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 08-11-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 08-12-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 08-27-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 08-28-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 09-15-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 09-17-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 10-06-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 10-12-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 12-21-2015 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 04-04-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 04-07-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 05-03-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 06-28-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 (CPNI)// // Updated 07-19-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 07-22-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 07-25-2016 | Ashley Long - AL201Q // // Updated 08-09-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // // Updated 09-15-2016 | Keith Davis - KD5879 // if (location.pathname == '/Common/about\_us/privacy\_policy/print\_policy.html') { pid = 'printversion'. } else { var url = location.href. pid = url.split('='). pid = pid\[1\]. checkAnc = pid.indexOf('#'). if(checkAnc != '-1') { pid = pid.split('#'). pid = pid\[0\]. } } //alert(pid). function renderPrintLink() { document.write ('' + 'View our current policy' + ''). } function renderLandingPageContent() { document.write(' ' + ' About Our Privacy Policy' + '

Whenever you do something like buy one of our products, watch a show or download an app, information is created. Because we know your privacy is important, we have a Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use and protect that information. There’s a quick summary below, and the actual policy is written in an easy to understand “Frequently Asked Questions” (FAQ) format. We want to simplify this explanation, so you can make informed choices about your privacy, and then spend the rest of your time enjoying our products and services.

' + '

**Effective July 24, 2015**

' + ' A Quick Summary of Our Privacy Policy' + '

Our Privacy Policy applies to your use of all products, services and websites offered by AT&T and our AT&T affiliates, such as DIRECTV, unless they have a different privacy policy. We will always provide you with notice of material changes to this Policy. In order to do things like constantly improve our services, products and relationship with you, we may collect different types of information that help us learn more about how our offerings are used.

' + '

**Our privacy commitments**

' + '

' + '*   We don’t sell your Personal Information to anyone for any purpose. Period.
' + '*   We keep your Personal Information in our business records while you are a customer, or until it is no longer needed for business, tax or legal purposes.
' + '*   We will keep your information safe using encryption or other appropriate security controls.
' + '

' + '

**Here’s some of the information we collect:**

' + '

' + '*   **_Account Information_** includes your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, service-related details such as payment data, security codes, service history and other information like that;
' + '*   **_Network Performance_** **_&. Usage Information_** tells us how you use our networks, our products and our services, and how well our equipment and networks are performing;
' + '*   **_Web Browsing &. Wireless Application Information_** tells us about the websites you visit and the mobile applications you use on our networks.
' +'*   **_Location Information_** tells us where your wireless device is located, as well as your ZIP-code and street address;
' + '*   **_TV Viewing Information_** tells us about which programs you watch and record and similar information about how you use our video services and applications.
' + '

' + '

**Here are the three basic ways we collect it:**

' + '

' + '*   We get information from you when you do things like make a purchase from us.
' + '*   We collect it from how you use our products and services;
' + '*   We obtain information from other sources, like credit agencies, marketing companies, and other service providers.
' + '

' + '

**Here are just some of the ways we use it. To:**

' + '

' + '*   Provide services and improve your customer experience;
' + '*   Send you bills for your services;
' + '*   Respond to your questions;
' + '*   Address network integrity, help in fraud prevention and network and device security issues;
' + '*   Do research and analysis to maintain, protect, develop and improve our networks and services;
' + '*   Let you know about service updates, content, offers and promotions that may be of interest to you;
' + '*   Improve entertainment options;
' + '*   Deliver Relevant Advertising;
' + '*   Create External Marketing &. Analytics Reports;
' + '*   Assist in the prevention and investigation of illegal activities and violations of our Terms of Service or Acceptable Use Policies.
' + '

' + '

**Some examples of who we share your Personal Information with:**

' + '

' + '*   **Across our companies** to give you the best customer experience and to help you get everything we have to offer.
' + '*   **Other, non-AT&T companies that perform services on our behalf** only as needed for them to perform those services. We require them to protect your information consistent with our Policy.
' + '*   **With other companies and entities, to**:
' + '

' + '*   Respond to 911 requests and other emergencies or exigencies;
' + '*   Comply with court orders and other legal process.
' + '*   Assist with identity verification, and preventing fraud and identity theft;
' + '*   Enforce our agreements and property rights. and
' + '*   Obtain payment for products and services including the transfer or sale of delinquent accounts to third parties for collection
' + '

' + '

' + '

**Understanding Personal, Anonymous &. Aggregate Information**

' + '

' + '*   What is Personal Information? Information that identifies or reasonably can be used to identify you.
' + '*   What is Anonymous Information? This is information that doesn’t identify you and can't reasonably be used to identify you specifically.
' + '*   What is Aggregate Information? We take a whole bunch of people’s data and combine it into anonymous groups or categories.
' + '*   How do we use this information? We use and share this information in many ways including research, analysis, retail marketing, and Relevant Advertising. This data is also included in External Marketing &. Analytics Reports.
' + '*   Want to learn more? Go here.
' + '

' + '

**Our Online Privacy Policy for Children**

' + '

' + '*   We want you to know that we don't knowingly collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of 13 unless we first obtain permission from the child's parent or legal guardian.
' + '

' + '

**Your Choices &. Controls**

' + '

' + '*   For information about children’s safety and parental controls, view our AT&T Smart Controls and DIRECTV Parental Controls.
' + '*   You have choices about certain types of advertising you get from us.
' + '*   You can control whether your anonymous information is used in our External Marketing &. Analytics Reports.
' + '*   You can choose whether to receive marketing calls, e-mails or text messages from us;
' + '*   You have a choice about how we use your Customer Proprietary Network Information.
' + '

' + '

Visit our Privacy Policy for more information.

' + '

'). var privacyFAQlink = ''. // alert (pid). if ( pid == '2506' ) { privacyFAQlink = '/gen/privacy-policy?pid=13692'. } document.write('*   Definitions
' + '*   Scope of this Policy
' /\* + '*   Scope of this Policy'). } else { document.write('Policy Scope">Policy Scope'). } document.write('
'\*/ + '*   The Information We Collect, How We Collect It, And How We Use It
' + '*   Information Sharing
' + '*   Online Activity Tracking and Advertising
' + '*   Location Information
' /\* + '*   Aggregate &. Anonymous Information'). } else { document.write('Information Sharing">Information Sharing'). } document.write('
'\*/ + '*   Aggregate and Anonymous Information
' + '*   External Marketing &. Analytics Reports
' + '*   Online Privacy Policy for Children
' /\* + '*   Online Privacy Policy for Children'). } else { document.write('Our Online Privacy Policy for Children">Our Online Privacy Policy for Children'). } document.write('
'\*/ + '*   Data Protection &. Security
' + '*   Changes
' /\* + '*   Changes'). } else { document.write('Changes">Changes to This Policy'). } document.write('
'\*/ + '*   Choices &. Controls
' /\* + '*   Customer Controls &. Choices'). } else { document.write('Customer Control">Choices &. Controls'). } document.write('
'\*/ + '*   How to Contact Us
' + '

' + '

**Your California Privacy Rights**

' + '

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 entitles California customers to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell your Personal Information to other companies and we will not share it with other companies for them to use for their own marketing purposes without your consent.

' + '

**California Web Site Data Collection &. "Do Not Track" Notices**

' + '

**Web Site Data Collection:** We do not knowingly allow other parties to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across third-party web sites when you use our websites and services. We provide information about the opt-out choices available to customers, and the opt-out choices provided by certain third-party website and mobile application analytics companies we use here.

' + '

**"Do Not Track" Notice:** Because the providers of "do not track" and similar signals do not yet operate according to common, industry-accepted standards, We currently do not respond to those signals. For more information on Do Not Track, please visit www.allaboutdnt.com.

' + '

California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with these requirements, or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact us at privacypolicy@att.com, or write to us at AT&T Privacy Policy, Chief Privacy Office, 208 S. Akard, Room 1033, Dallas, TX 75202.

' + ''). } function setFaqContent(sectionID) { document.getElementById(sectionID).scrollIntoView(true). menuItem = sectionID + 'A'. activeMenuItem = document.getElementById(menuItem). var menuItems = new Array('definitionsA','scopeA','collectA','locationA','trackingA','analyticsA','aggregateA','sharingA','childrenA','protectionA','controlsA','changesA','contactA'). for(m=0;m' + ' ' + '**Our AT&T Privacy Policy in easy to understand, FAQ format.**' + '

We understand that everyone thinks that privacy policies are long, complicated and difficult to understand. So we're going to try to make this as simple as possible.

' + '**What is the purpose of AT&T’s Privacy Policy?**' + '

Whenever you do something like buy or use one of our products or services or visit our websites, information is created. Because we know privacy is important to you, we have the AT&T Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and share that created information. Thus, the main purpose of the Policy is to help you understand our relationship and how we are able to deliver and improve the services we offer.

' + '**How should this Policy be used?**' + '

We encourage you to read the whole policy so you will understand fully our relationship. To find specific information, here is an outline of where you will find answers to your questions about key topics:

' + '

Visit these links for more information.

' + '

'). var privacyFAQlink = ''. // alert (pid). if ( pid == '2506' ) { privacyFAQlink = '/gen/privacy-policy?pid=13692'. } document.write('*   Definitions
' + '*   Scope of this Policy
' + '*   The Information We Collect, How We Collect It, And How We Use It
' + '*   Information Sharing
' + '*   Online Activity Tracking and Advertising
' + '*   Location Information
' + '*   Aggregate and Anonymous Information
' + '*   External Marketing &. Analytics Reports
' + '*   Online Privacy Policy for Children
' + '*   Data Protection &. Security
' + '*   Changes
' + '*   Choices &. Controls
' + '*   How to Contact Us
' + '

' + '**DEFINITIONS**' + '

**Let's start with what we mean when we say:**

' + '

**Aggregate Information:** We combine individual information into anonymous groups of customers or users. One way to think of it is in terms of a survey or opinion poll. Aggregate information would tell you that 80 percent of the people voted for a candidate, but not who actually voted. These groups are large enough to reasonably prevent individuals from being identified.

' + '

**Anonymous Information:** Information that doesn't directly identify and can't reasonably be used to identify an individual customer or user.

' + '

**AT&T:** Throughout this Policy, references to “AT&T,” “we,” “us,” and “our” include the family of AT&T companies around the world except affiliates who have a separate privacy policy.

' + '

**Customer:** Anyone who purchases or uses our products or services. When a customer purchases retail products or services for use by others, like a family account, those family members also are customers.

' + '

**Mobile Application:** A software application that runs on smartphones, tablet computers or other mobile devices and that allows users to access a variety of services and information.

' + '

**Personal Information:** Information that directly identifies or reasonably can be used to figure out the identity of a customer or user, such as your name, address, phone number and e-mail address. Personal Information does not include published listing information.

' + '

**Relevant Advertising:** Creates aggregate audience segments based on non-personally identifiable information about customers (like age, ethnicity, income range, a particular geographic area, and their interests) to serve advertising that is more likely to be useful to those audience segments. "Online behavioral advertising" is one type of Relevant Advertising. It uses interest categories based on the websites visited by people who are not personally identified to deliver advertising online.

' + '

**User:** Anyone who visits our websites or uses our mobile applications.

' + '

**Website:** And other terms like "Internet site," "site" and "web page" all mean the same thing, namely any page or location on the Internet, no matter what device (cell phone, tablet, laptop, PC, etc.) or protocol (http, WAP, ftp or other) is used to access the page or location.

' + '**QUESTIONS ABOUT THE SCOPE OF THIS POLICY**' + '

' + '1.  To whom does the Policy apply?
    
    ' + '

    This Privacy Policy applies to customers and users of AT&T products and services, except customers and users of products or services provided by an affiliate with a different privacy policy.
    
' + '2.  What does this Policy cover?
    
    ' + '

    This Privacy Policy covers our practices regarding the information we collect about our customers and users (how we collect it and how we use it). Use of our products and services, as well as visits to our websites, are subject to this Privacy Policy.
    
' + '3.  Do you have any Privacy Policies other than this one?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. Some AT&T affiliates may have separate privacy policies that describe how they collect, use and share information they collect from their customers and users. When we share Personal Information with those affiliates we require them to protect it in a way consistent with this Privacy Policy.
    
    ' + '

    Additionally, some of our applications may have terms and conditions that describe other privacy commitments or choices in addition to those in this Privacy Policy.
    
    ' + '

    Some areas outside the United States require us to work a little differently. In that case, we may adopt separate privacy policies as necessary to reflect the requirements of applicable local laws. Satellite TV subscribers in certain U.S. Territories also may have separate privacy policies.
    
    ' + '

    The Joint AT&T EchoStar Privacy Policy for AT&T|DISH Network Customer Account Information remains in effect for AT&T|DISH subscribers.
    
' + '4.  What about my family members and other users of my AT&T account? Does this Policy apply to them?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. You're responsible for making sure all family members or other users under your account understand and agree to this Policy. Get everyone together and talk about it. Or, send it by e-mail to make sure they're on board. Hang it on the fridge. Up to you, just share it!
    
' + '5.  When is information not covered by this Policy?
    
    ' + '

    If you purchase or use the products or services of an AT&T affiliate that has a different privacy policy than this one, that privacy policy will apply.
    
    ' + '

    Additionally, this Privacy Policy does not apply any time you give information to companies other than AT&T. Some examples are:
    
    ' + '
    ' + '  
    *   When you use a non-AT&T Wi-Fi service;
        
    ' + '*   When you download applications or make purchases from other companies while using our Internet or wireless services;
        
    ' + '*   When you go to a non-AT&T website from one of our websites or applications (by clicking on a link or an advertisement, for example);
        
    ' + '*   If you use public forums - such as social networking services, Internet bulletin boards, chat rooms, or blogs - the information is publicly available, and we cannot prevent distribution and use of that information by other parties;
        
    ' + '*   Information about your location, usage and the numbers you dial when you're out and about and roaming on the network of another company;
        
    ' + '*   When you purchase or use non-AT&T products (such as wireless devices, internet browsers and mobile applications) in combination with our services;
        
    ' + '*   When we license our brand to other companies for their use in marketing and selling certain non-AT&T products and services, information you give those companies is not covered by this Policy.
        
    ' + '' + '
6.  Can my information be covered by this Policy and other privacy policies at the same time?
    
    ' + '

    Yes, that can happen. For example:
    
    ' + '
    
    Sometimes we will work with other, unaffiliated companies to provide a service. In that case your information may be subject to this Policy and that of the other company. For example, if you use AT&T High Speed Internet services "powered by" Yahoo! Inc., your information may be covered by both this Policy and the Yahoo! Privacy Policy.
    
    ' + '

    If you purchase one of our products or services from a retailer like Best Buy or Amazon.com, for example, any information you provide to them may be subject to both their policy and ours.
    
    ' + '

    If you connect to our Wi-Fi service through another network, such as one provided in a hotel, airport or other venue, any information collected from your use of that network could be subject to either the AT&T Privacy Policy or the venue policy, and sometimes both. The same thing applies if you connect to our network through your employer's corporate network, or any network operated by a non-AT&T company.
    
    ' + '

    We think it's a great idea to take a look at the privacy policies of any companies you do business with to learn how they use your information.
    
' + '7.  What about business customers?
    
    ' + '

    We may have written product or service agreements with our business customers that contain specific provisions about confidentiality, security or handling of information. When one of these agreements differs from or conflicts with this Policy, the terms of those agreements will apply. In all other instances, the terms of this Policy apply.
    
' + '

' + '**QUESTIONS ABOUT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE COLLECT IT AND HOW WE USE IT**' + '

' + '1.  What information do you collect?
    
    ' + '

    We may collect different types of information based on your use of our products and services and on our business relationship with you.

    ' + '
    ' + '*   **Account Information:**
        
        ' + '
        ' + '*   **Contact Information** that allows us to communicate with you. We get this information when you order or register for our services. This would include information like your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address.
            
        ' + '*   **Billing Information** related to your financial relationship with us, such as the services we provide to you, the telephone numbers you call and text, your payment history, your credit history, your credit card numbers, Social Security number, security codes and your service history.
            
        ' + '
    ' + '*   **Technical &. Usage Information** related to the services we provide to you, including information about how you use our networks, services, products or websites. Some examples include:
        
        ' + '
        ' + '*   **Equipment Information** that identifies the equipment on our networks, such as equipment type, device identifiers, device status, serial numbers, settings, configuration and software.
            
        ' + '*   **Network Performance &. Usage Information** about the operation of the equipment, services and applications you use on our networks. Examples of this might include wireless device location, the number of text messages sent and received, voice minutes used, calling and texting records, bandwidth used, and resources you use when uploading, downloading or streaming data to and from the Internet. We also collect information like transmission rates and delays, data associated with remote monitoring services and security characteristics.
            
            ' + '
            *   ' + '
                
                Some Network Performance &. Usage Information and some Billing Information is **Customer Proprietary Network Information or "CPNI."** Unique rules apply to CPNI. Go here to learn more about what it is, how we use it and the choice you can make about that use.
                
                ' + '
        ' + '*   **Web Browsing &. Mobile Application Information** such as IP addresses, URLs, data transmission rates and delays. We also learn about the pages you visit, the time you spend, the links or advertisements you see and follow, the search terms you enter, how often you open an application, how long you spend using the app and other similar information.
            
        ' + '
    ' + '*   **Location Information** includes your ZIP-code and street address, as well as the whereabouts of your wireless device. Location information is generated when your device communicates with cell towers, Wi-Fi routers or access points and/or with other technologies, including the satellites that comprise the Global Positioning System.
        
    ' + '*   **TV Viewing Information** is generated by your use of any of our satellite or IPTV (U-verse) services. These services may include video on demand, pay per view, DVR services, applications to watch your TV on the go for tablet or smartphone (such as the TV Everywhere app) and similar AT&T services and products, including the programs and channels you and those in your household watch and record, the times you watch and how long you watch. It also includes information like the interactive channels and games provided by U-verse or DIRECTV. We also collect information related to your use and interaction with the equipment in your home, including the TV receivers, set top boxes, remotes and other devices you may use to access our services.
        
    ' + '
' + '2.  How Do You Collect Information?
    
    ' + '

    In three basic ways:  

    ' + '
    ' + '*   **You Give It To Us** when you make a purchase or set up an account with us.
        
    ' + '*   **We Automatically Collect Information** when you use our networks, products and services. For example, we use network tools to collect your call records. we collect wireless device location from our networks and from your device. and we also use cookies, web server logs and other technologies.
        
    ' + '*   **We Obtain Information from Outside Sources** like credit reports, marketing mailing lists, and commercially available geographic and demographic information along with other publicly available information, such as public posts to social networking sites.
        
    ' + '
' + '3.  How Do You Use This Information?  

    ' + '
    
    We use your information to improve your experience and to make our business stronger. Some examples include:  

    ' + '
    ' + '*   Providing and managing your services, responding to your questions and addressing problems;
        
    ' + '*   Delivering customized content, or advertising, such as personalized offers for products and services that may be of interest to you;
        
    ' + '*   Communicating service updates, offers and promotions;
        
    ' + '*   Protecting network integrity and security, ensuring quality control, optimizing capacity and preventing misuse;
        
    ' + '*   Network enhancement planning, engineering and technical support;
        
    ' + '*   Conducting research and analysis for maintaining, protecting and developing our networks and our services;
        
    ' + '*   Preventing illegal activities, suspected fraud, and potential threats to our networks and our customers’ networks;
        
    ' + '*   Investigating violations of our Terms of Service, Acceptable Use Policies, or other service conditions or restrictions. and
        
    ' + '*   Protecting the safety of any person.
        
    ' + '
' + '4.  Do you use the information I store using one of your cloud services?
    
    ' + '

    We only use it to provide you with that service, unless we first get your permission to use it for something different.
    
' + '

' + '**QUESTIONS ABOUT INFORMATION SHARING**' + '

' + '1.  Do you provide information for phone books and Caller ID?
    
    ' + '

    Yes and No.
    
    ' + '

    Yes, we share the names, addresses and telephone numbers of our wireline telephone and U-verse Voice customers with businesses that publish directories and provide directory assistance services. We are required by law to do that. We honor your request for non-published or non-listed phone numbers. Once we provide published listing information to those businesses, they may use, sort, package, repackage and make it available again in different formats to anyone.
    
    ' + '

    Yes, we also provide wireline and wireless calling name and number information for CallerID, and related services like Call Trace, which allow a person receiving a call to obtain the name and number of the party calling them.
    
    ' + '

    No, we do not give listing information for wireless numbers to phone book publishers or directory assistance services without your permission.
    
' + '2.  Do you share my Personal Information internally?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. Our products and services are developed, managed, marketed and sold by a variety of our affiliated companies. We may share Personal Information internally, including with our affiliated companies that have a different privacy policy. When we share information with affiliates having a different privacy policy, we require them to protect it in a way consistent with this Privacy Policy. Sharing this information helps us offer you the high quality, seamless and innovative range of products you have come to expect from us. Some of these include:  

    ' + '
    
    ' + '*   Wireless voice, data, Internet, home security, automation and remote monitoring services provided by AT&T Mobility and AT&T Digital Life; and
        
    ' + '*   ' + '
        
        The suite of satellite and IPTV services, Voice and High Speed Internet Access services offered by our companies.
        
    ' + '
    
    ' + '
    
    If one of our subsidiaries does not operate under the AT&T brand, information sharing with that subsidiary is handled as though it is a non-AT&T company.
    
' + '3.  Do you share my Personal Information with other non-AT&T companies for them to market to me?
    
    ' + '

    We will only share your Personal Information with other non-AT&T companies for them to use for the marketing of their own products and services when we have your consent.
    
    ' + '
4.  Are there any other times when you might provide my Personal Information to other non-AT&T companies or entities?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. We share your Personal Information with other, non-AT&T companies that perform services for us, like processing your bill. Because we take our responsibility to safeguard your Personal Information seriously, we do not allow those companies to use it for any purpose other than to perform those services, and we require them to protect it in a way consistent with this Privacy Policy.
    
    ' + '

    Companies that perform these services may be located outside the United States or the jurisdiction where you reside. If your Personal Information is shared with these companies, it could be accessible to government authorities according to the laws that govern those jurisdictions.
    
    ' + '

    There are also occasions when we provide Personal Information to other non-AT&T companies or other entities, such as government agencies, credit bureaus and collection agencies, without your consent. Some examples include sharing to:  

    ' + '
    ' + '*   Comply with court orders, subpoenas, lawful discovery requests and other legal or regulatory requirements, and to enforce our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
        
    ' + '*   Obtain payment or make refunds for products and services that appear on your AT&T billing statements, including the transfer or sale of delinquent accounts or refund obligations to third parties for collection or payment;
        
    ' + '*   Enforce our agreements and protect our rights or property;
        
    ' + '*   Assist with identity verification and e-mail address validation.
        
    ' + '*   Notify, respond or provide information (including location information) to a responsible governmental entity in emergency or exigent circumstances or in situations involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury. and
        
    ' + '*   Notify the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children of information concerning child pornography of which we become aware through the provision of our services.
        
' + '5.  Do you share my personally identifiable TV Viewing Information with other, non-AT&T companies?
    
    ' + '

    We don't share your personally identifiable TV Viewing Information with other non-AT&T companies for them to use for the marketing of their own products and services without your consent. We are required to notify you about the special requirements we must follow when it comes to sharing your personally identifiable TV Viewing Information in response to a Court Order:
    
    ' + '
    
    **Notice Regarding Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information of Satellite and IPTV Subscribers in Response to A Court Order**  

    ' + '
    ' + '*   In the case of a court order obtained by a non-governmental entity, we are authorized to disclose personally identifiable information collected from TV subscribers as a result of the subscriber's use of TV service only after providing prior notice to the subscriber.
        
    ' + '*   In the case of a court order obtained by a governmental entity, we are authorized to disclose personally identifiable information collected from TV subscribers as a result of the subscriber's use of TV service only if, in the court proceeding relevant to the order:  

        ' + '
        ' + '*   The governmental entity offers clear and convincing evidence that the subject of the information is reasonably suspected of engaging in criminal activity and that the information sought would be material evidence in the case. and
            
        ' + '*   The subject of the information has an opportunity to appear and contest the governmental entity's claim. and
            
        ' + '*   We have provided notice to the subscriber as required by applicable state law.
            
        ' + '
' + '

' + ' **QUESTIONS ABOUT MY INFORMATION &. ADVERTISING**' + '

' + '1.  Do you use my information to send me advertising?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. We may use information like the preferences you have expressed and interests you have demonstrated on our websites, in our stores and through use of our products and services, to provide you with marketing information and advertisements for our products and services. Those ads may be delivered on our websites and mobile applications. This is called "first party" advertising. It is part of our service relationship and you are not able to opt-out from this type of advertising.
    
    ' + '

    We or our advertising partners may use anonymous information gathered through cookies and similar technologies, as well as other anonymous and aggregate information that either of us may have to help us tailor the ads you see on non-AT&T sites. For example, if you see an ad from us on a non-AT&T sports-related website, you may later receive an ad for sporting equipment delivered by us on a different website. This is called Online Behavioral Advertising, which is a type of Relevant Advertising.
    
' + '2.  Do you use my information for other types of Relevant Advertising?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. We may also use information we get through your use of our products and services, from our advertising partners, and information like your age and gender to deliver Relevant Advertising that is not Online Behavioral Advertising. We combine your anonymous information with that of other users into aggregate "audience segments". These segments are based on particular interests and/or factual characteristics that everyone in that audience segment is likely to share. We might use that information to send you advertisements that are relevant to those interests or characteristics.
    
    ' + '

    We are careful to only use non-personally identifiable information to create Relevant Advertising with aggregate audience segments that are large enough that you can't be identified individually.
    
' + '3.  Do you use the location of my device for advertising purposes?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. We use information about the locations you visit in order to create combined wireless location interest characteristics that can be used to provide Relevant Advertising to you and others like you.
    
    ' + '

    Location characteristics are types of locations - like "movie theaters". People who live in a particular geographic area (a city, ZIP-code or ZIP+ 4 code, for example) might appear to have a high interest in movies, thanks to collective information that shows wireless devices from that area are often located in the vicinity of movie theaters. We might create a "movies characteristic" for that area, and deliver movie ads to the people who live there.
    
    ' + '

    We may associate your wireless device with a particular geographic area, such as a city, ZIP-code, or ZIP + 4 code, based on your billing address or the cell towers you connect with most frequently.
    
    ' + '

    In addition to other privacy protections, the process we use to create our audience segment includes a requirement that the ZIP + 4 or other geographic area to which a wireless location is assigned must contain a minimum of 25 households. ZIP + 4 codes with less than 25 households are combined with other ZIP + 4 codes to satisfy this requirement.
    
' + '4.  What's in it for me?
    
    ' + '

    Just like the name says, you get advertising that's more relevant to your interests. For example, if a particular audience segment, like adults between the ages of 21 and 25 with a certain income range, has demonstrated a greater interest in movies than other segments, we might send them a movie ad for a movie geared toward young adults.This is just one way we deliver content that's more relevant.
    
' + '5.  How do you use information about the programs I watch on TV to advertise to me?
    
    ' + '

    We combine information about the shows that our customers are watching with their common interests to help us figure out what types of advertising they might be interested in seeing.
    
    ' + '

    It sometimes works like this: We look at the group of people watching a particular show. We identify common characteristics within that group. We use those characteristics to identify and deliver advertising that might be most relevant to watchers of that TV show. We might also deliver that same advertising during shows that appear to have similar audiences.
    
' + '6.  Do I ever have a chance to tell you what I'm personally interested in?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. With some programs offered or powered by AT&T you can sign up to receive text-message offers from businesses that are near your current location and match the interests you've selected. You can change your mind at any time and stop participating in these programs.
    
    ' + '

    When we add new offers like Internet Preferences we'll let you know, so you can decide if you'd like to participate. For example, we may offer you free or discounted services in exchange for the use of your Personal Information for advertising and other similar purposes. We promise, before we use any of your Personal Information (including information we gather as an Internet service provider) for such purposes, we will always give you the opportunity to make an informed choice about whether to participate
    
' + '7.  What information do you provide to advertisers?
    
    ' + '

    We may provide reports to advertisers and other business customers about the success of its advertising campaigns. Those reports contain aggregate information about the number of times a particular ad was viewed, when it was viewed, whether it was viewed on a TV, a mobile device or a computer, demographics associated with the viewing audience and other similar information. Your anonymous information will not be included in aggregate reports about the success of Relevant Advertising campaigns if you have opted-out of Relevant Advertising delivered by AT&T.
    
' + '

' + '**QUESTIONS ABOUT LOCATION INFORMATION**' + '

' + '1.  What is location information?
    
    ' + '

    Exactly what it sounds like! It includes your ZIP-code and street address, as well as the whereabouts of your wireless device.
    
' + '2.  How is it used?
    
    ' + '

    We use it in all kinds of ways, here are some examples:

    ' + '
    ' + '*   **We Provide Wireless Voice and Data Services**: We monitor, collect and use wireless location information, together with other information we get from our network and your wireless device, to maintain and improve our network. We also might use location information with your consent to provide you with a customized experience. For example, when you dial 411 Directory Assistance for a business telephone number, we might use your wireless location information to return the number of the business location closest to you.
        
    ' + '*   **Location Based Services (LBS):** Your device can be used to access a ton of services based on location. We offer these services via applications that have been pre-loaded or downloaded by you on your device. LBS also may be provided via text message or other functionality. We’ll give you prior notice and ask for your consent when your location is used or shared. The form of consent may vary, but will be appropriate for the type of LBS you use.
        
    ' + '*   **LBS from other providers**: With your consent (to us or the other company) we also may enable LBS from other companies by providing location information to their developers or location service providers.
        
    ' + '*   We use it for Advertising
        
' + '3.  How accurate is wireless location information?
    
    ' + '

    It depends on the technology we're using. For example, we can locate your device based on the cell tower that's serving you. The range could be up to 1,000 meters in any direction from the tower in urban areas, and up to 10,000 meters in rural areas. Wi-Fi networks provide more accurate location information, associating you with the place where the network is located - like a coffee shop - or to an area within or around that place.
    
    ' + '

    Services such as 411, 911, a "friend locator" application or a navigation/mapping application, require more precise information. So for those we develop a more precise estimate of location by associating the serving cell tower ID with other information, like the latitude and longitude of the tower, radio frequency parameters, GPS information and timing differences in radio signals. Depending on a variety of factors, those methods may estimate the location of your device to within 30 to 1000 meters.
    
' + '4.  Are you the only ones who can locate my wireless device?
    
    ' + '

    Other companies may also be able to locate your device. For example, your handset manufacturer and your operating system provider may be able to locate your device. If you download mobile applications, those apps may be able to obtain your location directly from your handset or the operating system. Mobile applications that give you access to your employer's network may also give your employer the ability to locate your device.
    
    ' + '
    
    We urge you to review policies of all providers.
    
' + '

' + ' **QUESTIONS ABOUT AGGREGATE AND ANONYMOUS INFORMATION**' + '

' + '1.  Where do you get anonymous information?
    
    ' + '

    Sometimes we'll collect information about how you use our products using cookies and other similar technologies. This information doesn't include your Personal Information and is considered anonymous.
    
    ' + '

    When we collect information that identifies you personally, we may anonymize it for certain purposes. We remove data fields (such as name, address and telephone number) that can reasonably be used to identify you. We also use a variety of statistical techniques and operational controls to anonymize data. Anonymizing information is one of the tools we use to protect your privacy.
    
' + '2.  Tell me more about aggregate information.
    
    ' + '

    Aggregate information is a form of anonymous information. We combine data that meet certain criteria into anonymous groups. For example, we might want to compare how customers in Beverly Hills, CA (or any city, county or ZIP-code) use their cell phones to how customers in Boulder, CO use their cell phones. In order to do that, we would combine customer data in each of the geographies into anonymous groups and look at all that aggregate data to understand how the two groups are different or similar.
    
' + '3.  Do you share anonymous or aggregate information?
    
    ' + '

    Yes, we may share this information with other companies and entities for specific uses, which may include:

    ' + '
    
    ' + '*   Universities, laboratories, think tanks and other entities that conduct networking, social, behavioral, environmental and other types of scientific research, for the purpose of creating fundamental new knowledge;
        
    ' + '*   Municipalities, government or other entities that may use this data for purposes such as municipal and transportation planning, and emergency and disaster response coordination.

    ' + '
    
    We share this information in external reports like our External Marketing &. Analytics Reports and Metric Reports.
    
' + '

' + ' **QUESTIONS ABOUT EXTERNAL MARKETING AND ANALYTICS REPORTS**' + '

' + '1.  Tell me more about the External Marketing &. Analytics Program.
    
    ' + '

    We use aggregate information to create External Marketing &. Analytics Reports that we may sell to other companies for their own marketing, advertising or other similar uses.
    
    ' + '

    These reports may be a combination of information from wireless and Wi-Fi locations, TV Viewing, calling and texting records, website browsing and mobile application usage and other information we have about you and other customers. You have a choice about whether your anonymous information is included in the reports that we sell or provide to other companies.
    
    ' + '

    Some examples of External Marketing &. Analytics Reports include:

    ' + '
    ' + '*   Reports for retail businesses that show the number of wireless devices in or near their store locations by time of day and day of the week, together with demographic characteristics or other information about the users (such as device type, age or gender) in those groups.
        
    ' + '*   Reports that combine anonymous TV Viewing behaviors with other aggregate information we may have about our subscribers to create reports that would help a TV network better understand the audiences that are viewing their programs, those that are not, how frequently they watch, when they watch and other similar information; and
        
    ' + '*   Reports for device manufacturers that combine information such as device type, make and model with demographic and regional location information to reflect the popularity of particular device types with various customer segments.
        
' + '2.  Do you provide companies with individual anonymous data as part of your External Marketing &. Analytics Program?

    ' + '
    
    Yes. For example, we might share anonymous TV Viewing Information with media research companies that combine this data with other information to provide audience analysis services about what shows certain audience segments are watching. When we provide individual anonymous information to businesses, we require that they only use it to compile aggregate reports, and for no other purpose. We also require businesses to agree they will not attempt to identify any person using this information, and that they will handle it in a secure manner, consistent with this Policy.
    
' + '3.  Do you use my anonymous information in other types of external reports?

    ' + '
    
    Yes, we may use your anonymous information to provide Metrics Reports to our business customers and service suppliers. These reports are considered part of the underlying service and we do not sell them to other customers or suppliers.
    
    ' + '
    
    For example, if you connect to our Wi-Fi service in a hotel, airport or other venue you should know the operator of that venue is our business customer, and that we will provide that operator with Metrics Reports about usage of and communications with the Wi-Fi network in their location. Those reports contain statistical information like:

    ' + '
    
    ' + '*   The number of devices connecting to the Wi-Fi network, duration of Wi-Fi sessions and the amount of bandwidth used during those sessions. and
        
    ' + '*   Foot-traffic data, including the numbers of devices inside and outside the store at a given time. the number of new and frequent visitors. where visitors are located within the store (e.g., specific departments or other locations within the venue) and frequency of visits and time spent within the store.
        
    ' + '*   **NOTE:** When your wireless device is turned on, it regularly sends out signals that enable it to connect to cell towers, Wi-Fi access points or other technologies so that we (and others) are able to provide you with services. These signals can be used to determine your device location. You can turn Wi-Fi to the "off" position on the "settings" feature of your device to prevent the collection of these signals by Wi-Fi equipment in retail stores and other public places.

    ' + '
    
    Another example, we also license video programming from content providers. As part of our agreement, we provide them with Metrics Reports. These reports contain combined measurements and statistical information related to the number of TV subscribers who watched or accessed a particular program at a particular time and other similar measurements.
    
' + '

' + ' **QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY FOR CHILDREN**' + '

' + '1.  Do you collect information about my children's use?
    
    ' + '

    We do not knowingly collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of 13 unless we first obtain permission from the child's parent or legal guardian.
    
' + '2.  What happens when my child is using an account not registered to them?
    
    ' + '

    Internet and wireless devices and services purchased for family use may be used by children without our knowledge. When that happens, information collected may appear to us to be associated with the adult customer who subscribes to our services and will be treated as the adult's information under this Policy.
    
' + '3.  What can I do to help better protect my child's information?
    
    ' + '

    We encourage you to spend time online with your children, and to participate in and monitor their online activity. We have developed a website that offers safety and control tools, expert resources and tips designed to help you manage technology choices and address safety concerns. Please visit AT&T Smart Controls for more information.
    
' + '4.  What if my child has an AT&T e-mail sub-account?
    
    ' + '

    If you create an AT&T e-mail sub-account for a child under the age of 13:

    ' + '
    
    ' + '*   With your permission we collect your child’s name, nicknames and aliases, alternative e-mail address, birth date, gender and ZIP-code.
        
    ' + '*   We use the information collected on sub-accounts to create and maintain those accounts, for research, to customize the advertising and content seen on our pages and for other marketing purposes. Your child can use their AT&T e-mail address and password to log onto websites and online services provided by us, like uverse.com. We and our advertising partners may collect and use information about customers who log onto those sites as described in the "Questions about the Information We Collect, How we Collect It and How We Use It" section of this Privacy Policy. A list of the advertising partners who collect information on our sites and the ability to opt-out of advertising provided by those partners is available here.
        
    ' + '*   We will not contact a child under the age of 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without parental consent.
        
    ' + '*   You or your child can review, edit, update, and delete information relating to your child's sub-account and, if you no longer wish your child to have such an account, you can revoke your consent at any time, by logging on to manage your account here.
        
    ' + '
    
    ' + '
    
    You may e-mail us at privacypolicy@att.com, call us at 800.495.1547 or write to us at AT&T Privacy Policy, Chief Privacy Office, 208 S. Akard, Room 1033, Dallas, TX 75202 with any questions or concerns you may have about our Children's Online Privacy Policy.
    
' + '

' + ' **QUESTIONS ABOUT DATA PROTECTION AND SECURITY**' + '

' + '1.  Do we sell your Personal Information?
    
    ' + '

    No. We do not sell your Personal Information to anyone, for any purpose. Period.
    
' + '2.  How long do we keep your Personal Information?
    
    ' + '

    We keep your Personal Information as long as we need it for business, tax or legal purposes. After that, we destroy it by making it unreadable or undecipherable.
    
    ' + '
3.  What safeguards does AT&T have in place?
    
    ' + '

    We've worked hard to protect your information. And we've established electronic and administrative safeguards designed to make the information we collect secure. Some examples of those safeguards include:

    ' + '
    ' + '*   All of our employees are subject to the AT&T Code of Business Conduct (COBC) and certain state-mandated codes of conduct. Under the COBC, all employees must follow the laws, rules, regulations, court and/or administrative orders that apply to our business - including, specifically, the legal requirements and company policies surrounding the privacy of communications and the security and privacy of your records. We take this seriously, and any of our employees who fail to meet the standards we've set in the COBC are subject to disciplinary action. That includes dismissal.
        
    ' + '*   We've implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your Personal Information. Some examples are:

        ' + '
        ' + '*   Maintaining and protecting the security of computer storage and network equipment, and using our security procedures that require employee user names and passwords to access sensitive data;
            
        ' + '*   Applying encryption or other appropriate security controls to protect Personal Information when stored or transmitted by us;
            
        ' + '*   Limiting access to Personal Information to only those with jobs requiring such access. and
            
        ' + '*   Requiring caller/online authentication before providing Account Information so that only you or someone who knows your Account Information will be able to access or change the information.
            
        ' + '*   Although we strive to keep your Personal Information secure, no security measures are perfect, and we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Policy (for example, as the result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate the law or this Policy).
            
        ' + '
    ' + '
' + '4.  Will you notify me in case of a security breach?
    
    ' + '

    Laws and regulations guide us in how to give you notification when certain types of sensitive information are involved in a security breach. We will provide you with notice in accordance with these laws and regulations.
    
' + '5.  Can I review and correct my Personal Information?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. We are happy to help you review and correct the Personal Information we have associated with your account and billing records. Please contact us.
    
' + '6.  Have your privacy practices been certified?
    
    ' + '

    Yes, and we're very proud of it! TRUSTe has awarded us the TRUSTe Privacy Seal. As an independent third party, TRUSTe's mission is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions.
    
    ' + '

    Our TRUSTe Privacy Seal signifies that TRUSTe has reviewed our Privacy Policy and practices for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements. These include transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your Personal Information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through our certified web sites.
    
' + '

' + ' **QUESTIONS ABOUT FUTURE CHANGES**' + '

' + '1.  What happens if there is a change in corporate ownership?
    
    ' + '

    Information about our customers and users, including Personal Information, may be shared and transferred as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets or transition of service to another provider. This also applies in the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which customer and user records would be transferred to another entity as a result of such a proceeding.
    
' + '2.  Will I be notified if there are changes to this policy?
    
    ' + '

    We may update this Privacy Policy as necessary to reflect changes we make and to satisfy legal requirements. We will post a prominent notice of material changes on our websites. We will provide you with other appropriate notice of important changes at least 30 days before the effective date.
    
' + '

' + ' **YOUR CHOICES &. CONTROLS**' + '

' + '1.  You can choose not to receive some types of advertising online, on your satellite TV service or on your wireless device.

    ' + '
    ' + '*   Opt-out of Relevant Advertising delivered by AT&T here.
        
    ' + '*   Opt-out of Online Behavioral Advertising provided by AT&T and other advertisers on your computer by clicking the "Advertising Choices" link at the bottom of our web pages.
        
    ' + '*   Opt-out of interest-based advertising on att.net powered by Yahoo! here.
        
    ' + '*   Opt-out of online behavioral advertising from many other ad networks at the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) site.
        
    ' + '*   When you see online ads for AT&T products and services that display this icon , click and you will get information on how to opt-out.
        
    ' + '*   To limit collection of data on web sites that may be used for advertising, go here for information on how to manage cookies and other similar technologies on your computer.
        
    ' + '
' + '2.  Do I have choices about receiving first party advertisements from AT&T?
    
    ' + '

    Because first party advertising is part of the service you receive when you visit our websites and use our mobile applications, we don't offer an opt-out for first party advertising.
    
' + '3.  Can I choose not to receive other types of marketing from AT&T?
    
    ' + '

    We realize that unwanted marketing contacts can be a hassle and we've worked hard to meet the expectations of customers and potential customers who have expressed a desire to limit certain types of solicitation communications from us.
    
    ' + '

    **E-Mail:** Every marketing e-mail we send contains instructions and a link that will allow you to stop additional marketing e-mails for that product or service type. You also can unsubscribe from AT&T marketing e-mails here.
    
    ' + '

    **Text Messages**: Opt-out of AT&T marketing text message contacts by replying "stop" to any message.
    
    ' + '

    **AT&T Consumer Telemarketing:** Ask to be removed from our consumer telemarketing lists by contacting us at one of the numbers listed here. You also can ask the AT&T representative to remove you from our telemarketing lists when you receive a marketing or promotional call from us.
    
    ' + '

    **AT&T Business Telemarketing:** Where required by local laws and/or regulations, we honor requests to be removed from our telemarketing lists from business customers.
    
    ' + '

    **Federal Do Not Call:** The FTC maintains a National Do Not Call Registry at donotcall.gov, and some states in the United States may maintain its own Do Not Call Registry. Putting your number on these Registries also may limit our AT&T telemarketing calls to that number.
    
    ' + '

    **Postal Mail:** To review our Residential Do Not Mail Policy Statement and to limit postal mail solicitations, click here. You will still receive billing statements, legal notices, product updates and other similar correspondence, and you may still receive some promotional mailings.
    
    ' + '

    All of our practices are designed to satisfy state, provincial and federal legal requirements limiting marketing contacts. Those laws and regulations - such as the requirements governing the state and federal "Do Not Call" lists - generally permit companies to contact their own current and, in some cases, former customers, even when those customers are listed on the federal and state "Do Not Call" lists.
    
    ' + '

    Restricting our use of your CPNI will not eliminate all types of our marketing contacts.
    
' + '4.  Can I choose to exclude my anonymous information from your External Marketing &. Analytics and other similar reports?
    
    ' + '

    Yes. Click here to opt-out. This opt-out also applies to the sharing of your anonymous information with other companies for their use in creating marketing and analytics reports. Although this opt out does not apply to Metrics Reports, it will apply if we combine Metrics Report information with other customer information (like demographics) to create reports that we provide to our business customers or service suppliers.
    
' + '5.  What is DNS error assist?
    
    ' + '

    When you mistype a web address, or the address is not working, DNS Error Assist provides an automated list of similar pages – such as possibly the one you meant to type – for your consideration. The service is provided on your AT&T residential broadband connection, and you can opt-out here. If you opt-out, you will get a standard “no results found” error message instead of the error-assist page.
    
' + '6.  Are there any other opt-out choices I should know about?
    
    ' + '

    We may use services provided by analytics companies to obtain information about website performance and how you use our mobile applications and other products and services. Go here for more information about the opt-outs made available by some of those vendors, and to make choices about participation.
    
' + '7.  These Choices and Controls also are available at www.att.com/yourchoices.
    
' + '

' + ' **HOW TO CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY**' + '

' + '*   We encourage you to contact us directly at either of these addresses below for any questions about this Privacy Policy.

    ' + '
    *   E-mail us at privacypolicy@att.com
        
    ' + '*   Write to us at AT&T Privacy Policy, Chief Privacy Office, 208 S. Akard, Room 1033, Dallas, TX 75202.
        
' + '*   For questions not related to privacy click on the "Contact Us" link at the bottom of any att.com page. You also can access your online account from the upper right hand corner of our home page at att.com for additional service options.
    
' + '*   If you do not receive acknowledgment of your privacy inquiry or your inquiry is not addressed to your satisfaction, you may contact TRUSTe through the TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process. TRUSTe will serve as a liaison to resolve your concerns.
    
' + '*   You also have the option of filing a complaint with the FTC Bureau of Consumer Protection, using an online form, or by calling toll-free 877.FTC.HELP (877.328.4357. TTY: 866.653.4261). Other rights and remedies also may be available to you under federal or other applicable laws.
    
' + '*   If you are a satellite TV subscriber, you also have certain rights under Section 338(i) of the Federal Communications Act.
    
' + '

' + ' ' + ' '). } function renderCPNI() { document.write('What is CPNI?' + '

“CPNI” is information about your phone service from us. Your phone service could be a cell phone or any sort of home or business phone. The “information” is things like what kind of services you have, how you use them, or billing information. (Your telephone number, name and address are not considered CPNI.)

' + 'How is CPNI Used and Disclosed?' + '

We do not sell, trade or share your CPNI with anyone outside of the AT&T family of companies\* or our authorized agents, unless required by law (example: a court order).

' + '

We do use your CPNI internally, however. We may share information about our customers among the AT&T companies and our agents in order to offer you new or enhanced services. For example, we might offer a discount or promotion for Internet or TV services based on your CPNI.

' + 'How may I limit the use of my CPNI?' + '

AT&T uses technology and security features, and strict policy guidelines with ourselves and our agents, to safeguard the privacy of CPNI. It is your right and our duty under federal law to protect the confidentiality of your CPNI.

' + '

If you don’t want AT&T to use your CPNI internally for things like offers, here is what you can do:

' + '

' + '*   You can “opt out” online, at att.com/ecpnioptout, or
' + '*   You can call 800.315.8303, any time of day, and follow the prompts, or
' + '*   You can speak to a service representative at 800.288.2020 (consumer) or 800.321.2000 (business).
' + '*   For languages other than English and Spanish, please visit world.att.com.
' + '

' + '

If you choose to restrict our use of your CPNI, it won’t affect any of your services. You can change your mind at any time about allowing (or not allowing) us to use your CPNI, and we’ll honor your decision until you change it again. If you do restrict your CPNI use, you may still get marketing from us, but it won’t be from using CPNI.

' + '

\* The AT&T Family of Companies are those companies that provide voice, video and broadband-related products and/or services domestically and internationally, including the AT&T local and long distance companies, AT&T Corp., AT&T Mobility, DIRECTV, and other subsidiaries or affiliates of AT&T Inc. that provide, design, market, or sell these products and/or services.

' + ' ' + '

' + '

**Customer Service Contact Numbers**

' + '

**Wireless** - 1-800-331-0500

' + '

**Business** - 1-800-321-2000

' + '

**Residential** - 1-800-288-2020

' + '

**Spanish Language** - 1-800-870-5855

' + '

**Satellite TV Services** - 1-800-DIRECTV or 1-800-531-5000

' + '

For assistance in other languages, please visit world.att.com.

' + '

**Legacy AT&T Consumer** - 1-800-222-0300

' + '

**Customers of the following AT&T family of companies may contact us directly using the following:**

' + '

**AT&T Internet Services** - Customers can manage newsletter subscriptions or other e-mail communications from Yahoo! by modifying their AT&T Yahoo! Marketing Preferences.

' ). } function renderDNM() { document.write('

AT&T will maintain a company-specific (Internal) Do Not Mail (DNM) list of existing and prospective residential customers who request not to receive any AT&T marketing materials via US Postal Mail.' + '

' + '*   Consumers must contact the AT&T residential care center at 1-800-288-2020 and specify each individual member of the household and each associated address to be added to the DNM list.
' + '*   Generally AT&T processes DNM requests within 30 days. However, because our mailings are processed well in advance, you may continue to receive additional offers for some time after the request date.' + '
    ' + '*   Please note that AT&T may direct mail market to certain neighborhoods or zip codes. These offerings are delivered to all homes in a neighborhood or zip code. You may continue to receive this type of mailing even if you opt-out of receiving marketing related postal mailings from AT&T.
    ' + '' + '
' + '*   DNM requests for an individual consumer at a residential address will remain in effect for THREE years from the date of request.
' + '*   AT&T does not accept DNM requests from third party providers.
' + '*   AT&T DNM requests will expire upon change of address.
' + '

' + '

AT&T will not share or disclose DNM information with any third party other than AT&T vendors responsible for direct mail marketing on AT&T’s behalf.

' + '

Notifications and other non-solicitation mail pieces are exempt from this Consumer Marketing Residential DNM Policy.

' + '

AT&T reserves the right to discontinue this Consumer Marketing Residential DNM policy, and may cease accepting DNM requests or otherwise modify this Consumer Marketing Residential DNM policy.

'). } function renderCookies() { document.write('Definitions' + '

**Let's start with what we mean when we use the word "cookie" and other related terms:**

' + '

' + '*   **Cookies** are small data files. Websites place them in your browser to recognize your computer or mobile device when you return to that site. Cookies are created to keep track of your movements within the site, help you resume where you left off, remember your registered username, preferences and other customizations.
' + '*   There are a couple of important things to remember about cookies:
' + '

' + '*   Disabling cookies may prevent you from using specific features on some websites. You’ll need to perform the opt out procedure if you opt out of a program or service and then change computers or Web browsers, or clear or erase the digital "cookie" that lets us know you opted out.
' + '*   **Local Storage Cookies**. Local Storage is a convenient, flexible, secure and faster way to store HTTP state data. It is a method by which our web pages locally store named key/value pairs in a user’s web browser. Local storage on ATT.com is mainly used to store and retrieve data in HTML pages from our domains. Local storage data is session-based and will not persist once the session is over and the browser is closed.
' + '

' + '*   **Flash Cookies** (also called Local Shared Objects or "LSOs") are similar to cookies, except that they can store more complex data. They are used to remember your settings, preferences and usage, and other similar services. Flash cookies allow functionality and availability of certain services. If disabled, these services may not function correctly. While browser cookies may be removed or blocked via web browser settings, flash cookies operate differently. Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, To learn more about how to manage flash cookies, you can visit the Adobe website and make changes at Global Storage Settings Panel.
' + '*   **Web beacons** are small graphic images on a Web page or in an e-mail. They can be used for things like recording the pages and advertisements that users click on, or tracking how well an e-mail marketing campaign performs.
' + '*   A **widget** is a small program or application that can be embedded in a web page. It can provide real-time information, such as stock quotes or weather reports. Widgets are often provided by a third party and allow them to collect data about users viewing that page.
' + '*   A **server log** records your web activity by your computer or mobile device and plays a key role in improving web page performance and introducing new features. For example, it may record which search terms you’ve entered, or the links you’ve clicked on. It may also record your browser information, such as your IP address, device type, how long you spend on a Web page, and your browser's cookies.
' + '*   Some websites have “**social network or other third-party plug-ins.**” These plug-ins may provide information back to those sites, even if you don't click on or interact with the plug-in. It may also apply even if you don’t have an account with them. Social networks or third parties may use an identifier when transmitting from your browser. This might include information about your browser type, operating system, device type, IP address and the URL of the web page where the plug-in appears. If you use social networking tools or sites, we recommend you take a moment to familiarize yourself with their privacy policies.
' + '

' + 'Managing Cookies' + '

Most browsers will allow you to delete, disable and choose what cookies can be placed on your computer. If you want more information about controlling cookies, visit aboutcookies.org.

' + '

**To learn how to manage cookies for:**

' + '  
**Individual Browsers**' + '

' + '*   Internet Explorer »
' + '*   Internet Explorer (Mobile devices) »
' + '*   Safari »
' + '*   Safari Mobile (iPhones and iPads) »
' + '*   Firefox »
' + '*   Firefox (Mobile devices) »
' + '*   Chrome »
' + '*   Chrome (Mobile devices) »
' + '

' + '  
**Flash Player**' + '

*   adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security

'). } function renderOptOut() { document.write('

You have choices about how your information is collected and used, both by AT&T and by other companies. That includes "opting out" of some programs, setting privacy preferences, and unsubscribing from certain kinds of emails or letters. We've listed your choices below.

' + '

' + '*   **Relevant Advertising from AT&T:** You can opt-out of Relevant Advertising delivered by AT&T by going to Manage Your Privacy Choices.
' + '*   **Online Behavioral Advertising from AT&T and Other Advertisers:** You can opt out of online behavioral advertising from our advertising partners and others by going to Your Advertising Choices site. You will need to opt-out on each computer browser you wish to exclude.
' + '*   **Advertising on att.net**: You can opt-out of receiving targeted online ads from Yahoo! when using our att.net email service or other Yahoo! services by accessing ATT.net marketing preferences through your account.
' + '*   **Additional Advertising Opt-Out Choices:** You can opt out of online behavioral advertising from other companies who have joined an association called the Network Advertising Initiative.
' + '*   **Information about Cookies and Similar Technologies:** To limit collection of data on web sites that may be used for advertising, see the Definitions for information on how to manage cookies and other similar technologies on your computer.
' + '

' + '

Please keep in mind that in some cases, your choice will be linked to the specific phone, computer or web browser you're using, because that's how we know it's you. You’ll need to perform the opt out procedure again if you opt out of a program or service and then change computers or Web browsers, or clear or erase the digital "cookie" that lets us know you opted out.

' + '

**External Marketing &. Analytics Reports**

' + '

' + '*   You can choose to exclude your anonymous information from our External Marketing &. Analytics and similar reports by going to manage your privacy choices. Satellite TV only customers who have joined the AT&T Family of Companies can opt out www.att.com/directvprivacy.
' + '

' /\* \*/ + '

**Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI)**

' + '

' + '*   Go to CPNI Opt-Out, or go to https://www.wireless.att.com/ecpni/ for more information about CPNI and your choices about our use of that information for marketing purposes.
' + '

' + '

**DNS Error Assist**

' + '

' + '*   When you mistype a web address, or the address is not working, DNS Error Assist provides an automated list of similar pages – such as possibly the one you meant to type – for your consideration. The service is provided on your AT&T residential broadband connection, and you can opt-out by managing your privacy choices. You will get a standard “no results found” error message instead of the error-assist page.
' + '

' + '

**Other Marketing Communications Choices**

' + '

' + '*   **AT&T Marketing E-Mails**: You can opt-out of marketing emails by using email unsubscribe.
' + '*   **Postal Mail:** To review our Residential Do Not Mail Policy Statement and to limit postal mail solicitations, visit AT&T Consumer Marketing. You will still receive billing statements, legal notices, product updates and other similar correspondence, and you may still receive some promotional mailings.
' + '*   **Consumer Telemarketing:** Ask to be removed from our consumer telemarketing lists by contacting us at one of the numbers listed here, or by sending an e-mail to privacypolicy@att.com. You also can ask the AT&T representative to remove you from our telemarketing lists when you receive a marketing or promotional call from us.
' + '*   **Do Not Call**: The FTC maintains a National Do Not Call Registry at donotcall.gov, and your state may maintain its own Do Not Call Registry. Putting your number on these Registries also may limit our telemarketing calls to that number.
' + '

' + '

**Internet Preferences by U-verse with AT&T GigaPower**

' + '

U-verse with AT&T GigaPower customers can adjust their AT&T Internet Preferences selection at any time by calling AT&T Care at 866.324.4737. To learn more about U-verse with AT&T GigaPower Internet Preferences, visit att.com/internetpreferences.

' + '

**Opt-Outs for Analytics Services**

' + '

We may use services provided by analytics companies to obtain information about website performance and how you use our mobile applications and other products and services. We will provide links and other information related to the opt-outs that some of those providers make available to you.

' + '

*   AT&T uses applications provided by **Flurry and Crittercism** to obtain information about how our U-verse App for tablet and smartphone is used on customer wireless devices. **Flurry and Crittercism** are enabled by software embedded in the U-verse App that transmits information to their respective servers for analysis and reporting.' + '
    ' + '*   For more information about Flurry and its privacy policy, please go to https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/devel/details.html. If you do not want Flurry Analytics to collect information related to the use of the U-verse App from your device, you may opt out of Flurry data collection. If you opt-out, Flurry will cease collection of information related to your use of the U-verse App, as well as any other application on your device that contains the Flurry software agent.
    ' + '*   For more information about Crittercism and its privacy policy, please go to http://www.crittercism.com/privacy-policy If you do not want Crittercism to collect information related to the use of the U-verse App from your device, you may opt out of Crittercism data collection by going to "Settings" in the U-verse App, selecting "Diagnostics" and turning the toggle switch for "Enable Diagnostics" to "OFF". If you opt-out, the U-verse App will no longer send information to Crittercism.
    ' + '
' + '*   Criteo is a technology that anonymously measures advertising effectiveness. AT&T uses Criteo to measure the effectiveness of advertising shown on AT&T mobile applications. Learn more about Criteo, its privacy policy, and opt-out of its collection of information at http://www.criteo.com/privacy/. If you opt-out, AT&T mobile applications will no longer send anonymous information to Criteo.
' + '*   AT&T uses Adobe Analytics on some of its websites. Website visitors that don't want their visit data reported by the Adobe Analytics JavaScript can install the Adobe Analytics opt-out browser add-on. This add-on instructs the Adobe Analytics JavaScript to prohibit sending visit information to Adobe Analytics. The browser add-on is available for most modern browsers. The Adobe Analytics opt-out browser add-on does not prevent information from being sent to the website itself or in other ways to web analytics services.
' + '*   AT&T uses Google Analytics on some of its websites. Website visitors that don't want their visit data reported by the Google Analytics JavaScript can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. This add-on instructs the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) to prohibit sending visit information to Google Analytics. The browser add-on is available for most modern browsers. The Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on does not prevent information from being sent to the website itself or in other ways to web analytics services. Learn more about the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on.
' + '*   AT&T uses Tapad to establish connections between a user’s devices and to provide behavioral targeting across devices. Tapad uses industry standard identifiers for each specific device (cookies, Identifier for Advertisers (IDFA), etc.) Cross-device connections allow AT&T to understand that a single user is accessing AT&T services from multiple devices, and to synchronize content and advertising messages across those devices. To opt out of Tapad Please visit AT&T’s AdChoices on your PC or mobile device or http://www.tapad.com/privacy/ to opt out of Tapad’s Device GraphTM and learn more about how Tapad collects and uses data. If you opt-out of Tapad's Device GraphTM with a specific device, that device will no longer be associated with other devices for AT&T or any other Tapad client.
' + '*   AT&T uses Drawbridge to establish connections between a user’s devices and to provide behavioral targeting across devices. Drawbridge uses industry standard identifiers for each specific device (cookies, IDFA, etc.) Cross-device connections allow AT&T to understand that a single user is accessing AT&T services from multiple devices, and to synchronize content and advertising messages across those devices. To opt out of Drawbridge Please visit AT&T’s AdChoices on your PC or mobile device or http://www.drawbrid.ge/optoutstart to opt out of Drawbridge and learn more about how Drawbridge collects and uses data. You can also opt out through the AdChoices icon within the ad itself. If you opt-out of Drawbridge with a specific device, that device will no longer be associated with other devices for AT&T or any other Drawbridge client.
' + '

' ). } function renderEchoStar() { document.write('OUR COMMITMENT. RESPECTING AND PROTECTING OUR CUSTOMERS' PRIVACY ' + '

Your privacy is important to AT&T Home Entertainment (AT&T) and Echostar Satellite L.L.C. ("Echostar"-) (collectively "we" or "us"). We carefully ensure the confidentiality of each customer's account information. All AT&T and Echostar employees are specifically required to comply with legal requirements and their respective company policies relating to the privacy of communications and the security and privacy of customer records. Employees who fail to meet any of these policies may be subject to disciplinary action, including but not limited to dismissal.

' + 'THE SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY' + '

This Privacy Policy addresses the privacy of AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information. It identifies the type of data and Information we collect, how we use it, and the steps we take to protect privacy. AT&T Home Entertainment is a member of the AT&T family of companies and has agreed to the privacy practices in the AT&T Privacy Policy. AT&T and Echostar are individually responsible for complying with their respective obligations under this Joint Privacy Policy. Each party shall be solely liable for any failure to satisfy its obligations.

' + 'COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF AT&T | DISH NETWORK CUSTOMER ACCOUNT INFORMATION' + '

**Collection**  
AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information includes, but is not limited to: customer name, address, telephone number email address, demographic Information and AT&T | DISH Network billing, payment, transaction and programming Information. This Information is collected both during initial ordering and throughout the service relationship, including through interactive television transactions on AT&T | DISH Network.

' + '

**Use**  
We share AT&T | DISH Network Account Information with each other and with our affiliates. We and our affiliates use AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information to monitor quality of service and to provide service. We can identify you based on your receiver. We may use this ability combined with your AT&T IDISH Network Customer Account Information to display interactive television messages or advertisements on your television. AT&T and its affiliates and authorized agents may use AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information to market and sell AT&T-offered products and services (e.g., by mail or telephone). Echostar and/or its affiliates will not use AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information to market any additional products or services. We may use email addresses collected from customers to provide purchase confirmation and product/service information. Email addresses may also be used for marketing AT&T-offered products and services. We will not sell or provide customer email addresses to unaffiliated third parties for the marketing of their products.

' + '

**Disclosure**  
We may share necessary Information with outside parties, such as shipping companies or installation contractors, to complete an order, We may, where permitted by law, provide certain AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information to credit bureaus, or provide information and/or sell receivables to collection agencies, to obtain payment for services. We must disclose information when requested, to comply with court orders or subpoenas. We will also share information when necessary to prevent unlawful use of services, except as otherwise disclosed in this section. We will not sell or provide non-public AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information to unaffiliated third parties.

' + 'SECURITY' + '

We will keep AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information secure and confidential through safeguards such as secure encryption technology and by restricting access through the use of user names and passwords.

' + 'ACCESS' + '

You may access your AT&T | DISH Network Customer Account Information by calling 1-866 722-7500 to speak with an AT&T | DISH Network Customer Service Representative.

' + 'PRIVACY ON OTHER ORGANIZATIONS' APPLICATIONS' + '

AT&T | DISH interactive applications may be provided by third parties. Please be aware that when you visit other organizations' interactive television applications, you may be subject to the privacy policy of the new application. We recommend that you read the applicable privacy policy for all third-party applications in order to understand how they use your personal Information,

' + 'PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES' + '

If we decide to Change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this policy and other places we deem appropriate. If, however, we are going to use/disclose AT&T I DISH Network Customer Account Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify AT&T | DISH Network customers directly.

' ). } function renderPrivacyRightCol() { if (pid == '2506') { document.write(//'' //+ 'En Español' //+ 'En Français' // + '' // + '' // + '

Welcome DIRECTV Customers  
DIRECTV is now part of the AT&T family. For convenience, all AT&T products and services are covered under a single, easy-to-read Privacy Policy. The policy lays out our commitments to privacy and describes our policies for helping to protect personal information. We invite you to learn more about our commitments, safeguards and customer choices by reviewing our AT&T Policy, and we welcome your feedback.

' // + '

View the current AT&T privacy policy

' // + 'Welcome to the AT&T Privacy Policy,

effective date **11/18/2010**. We invite you to learn more about our commitments, safeguards and customer choices.

' // + '

**Welcome to the AT&T Privacy Policy. We will provide a preview of the updated privacy policy ��� before it goes into effect. Please check back soon for updates. The policy on these pages has an effective date of 11/18/2010.**

' // + '' '' + ' ' + '' + '

AT&T has been awarded the TRUSTe Privacy Seal and you may contact TRUSTe if a privacy question is not properly addressed

' + '' + '' + 'Your Rights and Choices' + '

You have choices about how your information is used and collected, both by AT&T and other companies.  
More

' + '

You can choose to be removed from call lists that we use to contact customers with marketing and promotional offers.  
More

' + '

We protect the confidentiality of your Customer Proprietary Network Information as required by law.  
More

' + '' /\*+ '' + '

The Ponemon Institute has named AT&T as one of the 20 most trusted companies on privacy for 2012.

' + ''\*/ + '' + '

**Lost or stolen phone?**  
For help on what to do, visit att.com/stolenphone.

' + '' + '' + '

**Please Be Aware** AT&T will never contact you by e-mail to ask for your personal information. If you receive such an e-mail, do not reply. Learn more about how to protect yourself from phishing attacks.

' + '' + '' + 'We Want to Hear  
from You' + '

Thanks for your feedback on our updated Privacy Policy. We heard you and, as a result, we're adding additional information on how you can exercise your privacy choices. We appreciate you as a customer and we value your thoughts. Please continue to share your feedback through our privacy mailbox.

' + '' + '' //+ '

Updated 5/21/15

' +'

**Q.** How is AT&T’s Privacy Policy different than DIRECTV’s?  
' +'

**A.** The AT&T Privacy Policy gives you an additional choice about how we use of your anonymous and aggregate information, for something we call “External Marketing &. Analytics Reports.” It also uses the term “Relevant Advertising” when describing advertising sent to audiences with common interests and characteristics.

' +'

**Q.** If I had previously chosen not to receive DIRECTV’s satellite TV advertising that is selected for me based on information about me, will AT&T honor my choice going forward?  
' +'

**A.** Yes. AT&T calls that Relevant Advertising, and we will continue to honor your previous choice going forward.

' +'

**Q.** What is your policy on limiting AT&T marketing materials sent by U.S. mail?  
' +'

**A.** Customers can unsubscribe from AT&T marketing materials sent by U.S. mail here.

' +'

**Q.** I have an AT&T business account. Will my anonymous information be used in External Marketing &. Analytics Reports?

' +'

**A.** These reports will use anonymous information from AT&T consumer accounts. Business accounts are not included except for small-business U-verse accounts. However, they can opt out just like consumer accounts by visiting www.att.com/cmpchoice.

' /\* +'

**Q.** For AT&T Relevant Advertising, why do I have to opt out from each computer or mobile device?

' +'

**A.** That's a good question. Opt-out works differently for your computer than for your mobile device. On your computer's web browser, opt-out works through a small data file called a "cookie." The cookie communicates from your browser, telling advertisers that you don't want to receive the relevant ad. It is anonymous, and is not linked to your identity or account. This is the current, standard method for online advertising. You can learn more about cookies here, and you can opt-out your computer's browser at http://www.att.com/internal/adchoices if you are on that computer now.

'\*/ +'

For mobile, different devices use different technologies. Some mobile devices, for example, do not support the use of cookies. Therefore, to ensure that we don't deliver AT&T Relevant Advertising to your mobile device, we must be able to accurately identify the device that you are opting out. To do that, on each device that you wish to opt-out, go to http://www.att.com/internal/adchoices and click "Opt-Out". Please make sure you are connected to the AT&T cellular network when you do so.

' +'

**Q.** I can't figure out how to opt out of the External Marketing &. Analytics Reports.

' +'

**A.** You can opt out of External Marketing &. Analytics reports in two ways. You can go to http://att.com/cmpchoice with your account ID and password, or you can call 866.344.9850. If you have more than one AT&T account, such as wireless and AT&T U-verse, you may have to log in to each account if you use att.com/cmpchoice. We require logging in for security, to make sure it's really you making a change to your account.

' +'

' + '' + '' + ' '). } else { document.write(''). if (pid == '13692') { document.write('En Español' + 'En Français'). } else if (pid == '11561') { document.write('En Español' + 'En Français'). } document.write('Return to Privacy Policy Home' + ''). document.write('' + ' ' + '' + '

AT&T has been awarded the TRUSTe Privacy Seal and you may contact TRUSTe if a privacy question is not properly addressed

' + '' +'' + 'Your Rights and Choices' + '

You have choices about how your information is used and collected, both by AT&T and other companies.  
More

' + '

You can choose to be removed from call lists that we use to contact customers with marketing and promotional offers.  
More

' + '

We protect the confidentiality of your Customer Proprietary Network Information as required by law.  
More

' + '' ). document.write('' + 'More Information' + '

Visit www.att.net/smartcontrols for tips on keeping your family safe while staying connected, and links to more safety resources.

' + '

Learn more about Smart Limits parental controls for Internet, wireless, television and home phone.

' ). } if (pid == '2566') {} else { // document.write('

We protect the confidentiality of your Customer Proprietary Network Information as required by law.  
More

'). } document.write(' '). /\*if(pid=='13692') { document.write('' + 'More Information' + '

Visit www.att.net/smartcontrols for tips on keeping your family safe while staying connected, and links to more safety resources.

' + '

Learn more about Smart Limits parental controls for Internet, wireless, television and home phone.

' + ' '). } else {} \*/ }
